mixin ListStroage {
  List<String> LevelNo = [
    'Level 1',
    'Level 2',
    'Level 3',
    'Level 4',
    'Level 5',
    'Level 6',
    'Level 7',
    'Level 8',
    'Level 9',
    'Level 10',
    'Level 11',
    'Level 12',
    'Level 13',
    'Level 14',
    'Level 15',
    'Level 16',
    'Level 17',
    'Level 18',
    'Level 19',
    'Level 20',
  ];


  List<Map<String,String>> levels= [
    {'question':'2 + 2 * 2 = ?','answer':'6'},
    {'question':'9 + 2 * 9 = ?','answer':'27'},
    {'question':'2,4,6,8, = ?','answer':'10'},
    {'question':'9,18,27,36 = ?','answer':'45'},
    {'question':'11,22,33,44= ?','answer':'55'},
    {'question':'5 + 5 * 5 - 5 =?','answer':'25'},
    {'question':'A + B =60\nA - B =40\nA / B = ?','answer':'5'},
    {'question':'13,18 =31\n7,25 =32\n12,30 =42\n26,13 =?','answer':'39'},
    {'question':'8 - 8 / 4 * 3 =?','answer':'2'},
    {'question':'11,15,20 =?','answer':'26'},
    {'question':'4,8 =32\n5,3 =15\n10,2 =20\n8,6 =?','answer':'48'},
    {'question':'4,8,16, =?','answer':'32'},
    {'question':'7,15,31, =? ','answer':'63'},
    {'question':'1 + 25 / 25 - 5 =?','answer':'21'},
    {'question':'7,14,21,28, =?','answer':'35'},
  ];
}